{
    "subject": "resource/Abbas_Saad",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Lebanon",
    "human_readable": "Abbas Saad was born in Lebanon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9149904847145081,
            "question": "Is Abbas Saad from Lebanon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8441424369812012,
            "question": "Where was Abbas Saad born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5768094658851624,
            "question": "What country is associated with Abbas Saad's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33231669664382935,
            "question": "Where might Abbas Saad have spent his early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24275438487529755,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Abbas Saad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22264449298381805,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Lebanon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18754476308822632,
            "question": "What cultural influences might have shaped Abbas Saad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15296046435832977,
            "question": "Is Lebanon known for its diverse population?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14897190034389496,
            "question": "What is the capital of Lebanon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1164943128824234,
            "question": "What are some popular traditions in Lebanon?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Abbas Saad was born in Lebanon.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8969_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the capital of Lebanon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8969_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Lebanon known for its diverse population?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8969_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What cultural influences might have shaped Abbas Saad?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8969_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8969_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8969_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8969_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8969_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8969_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8969_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8969_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8969_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8969_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8969_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Abbas Saad was indeed born in Lebanon. This information is mentioned in multiple documents (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8969/re-ranker-msmarco/55.txt and others)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that \"Abbas Saad Born in Lebanon,\" which supports the statement that Abbas Saad was born in Lebanon."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}